<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>All &#8211; New Talis US</title>
	<atom:link href="https://new.talis-us.com/category/all/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://new.talis-us.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 09:55:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://new.talis-us.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/New.png</url>
	<title>All &#8211; New Talis US</title>
	<link>https://new.talis-us.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>On this day in history: Pluto is a dwarf planet</title>
		<link>https://new.talis-us.com/on-this-day-in-history-pluto-is-a-dwarf-planet/</link>
					<comments>https://new.talis-us.com/on-this-day-in-history-pluto-is-a-dwarf-planet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 09:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Egypt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[On this day in history]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://new.talis-us.com/?p=1051</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Various incidents and accidents happen in the world every day. Many things are invented. Many are born and die. Do we remember all the daily events? However, some things [&#8230;]</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Various incidents and accidents happen in the world every day. Many things are invented. Many are born and die. Do we remember all the daily events? However, some things are permanently etched in people&#8217;s minds, some events go down in the pages of history. Our regular event &#8216;This Day in History&#8217; deals with such issues. Today is August 24. Let&#8217;s see what happened in the world today. Translated from the book &#8216;On This Day: A History of the World in 366 Days&#8217; by <strong>Anindya Saimum</strong>.</p>



<p>Pluto is the most distant planet in the solar system. This is what was written on the pages of the book earlier. On August 24, 2006, Pluto lost its status as a planet. This is because the earlier formal definition of a planet has been changed. Pluto is no longer included as a planet because it does not match the characteristics specified in the new definition. Pluto has since been called a minor planet or dwarf planet.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Finding Ancient Egyptian Inscriptions</h2>



<p>Osiris is the god of death in ancient Egyptian civilization. There is a temple of this deity in the country. The ancient Egyptians made various carvings on the walls of the temple. Made the inscription. On this day in 394 AD an inscription was recovered from the temple of the ancient Egyptian god of death. It was the last inscription written in the hieroglyphic system.</p>



<p>The time was August 24, 1967. London in the United Kingdom is on fire. The life of people suffering in extreme heat. Zoo animals were not left out. At that time there were two penguins at Chessington Zoo. It is quite difficult for penguins who are used to living in freezing cold environment to bear such heat. Essentially two penguins are taken out of the zoo and brought to the ice rink. They join the body there.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Signing of the Cordoba Treaty</h2>



<p>Mexico was once ruled by Spain, the European colonial power. On this day in 1821, the historic Treaty of Cordoba was signed. In the light of this agreement, Mexico was freed from the rule of Spain.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://new.talis-us.com/on-this-day-in-history-pluto-is-a-dwarf-planet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
